Guide to the Edmund Clarence Stedman Papers
Rare Book and Manuscript Library Columbia University Libraries
- Series I: Correspondence, Manuscripts, and Diaries
  - De Vinne, Theodore Low (Box 26)
  - Devyr, Thomas Ainge (Box 26)
  - Dewey, C.P. (Box 26)
  - Dewey, George (Box 26)
  - Dewey, Henry E. (Box 26)
  - De Witt, G.R. (Box 26)
  - DeWolfe Fiske & Co. (Box 26)
  - Dexter, Franklin Bowditch (Box 26)
  - Dibble, Harvey M. (Box 27)
  - Dibble, W.E. (Box 27)
  - Dickerson, J.J. (Box 27)
  - Dickey, J.S. (Box 27)
  - Dickey, John M. (Box 27)
  - Dickinson, Charles Monroe (Box 27)
  - Dickinson, Ellen E. (Box 27)
  - Dickinson, S. O’H (Miss) (Box 27)
  - Dill, Charles G. (Box 27)
  - Dillingham, George W. (Box 27)
  - Dimmock, M.J. (Box 27)
  - Dinnies, Anna Peyre (Box 27)
  - Dissette, E.H. (Box 27)
  - Dix, John Adams (Box 27)
  - Dix, Morgan (Box 27)
  - Dix, William Gilles (Box 27)
  - Dixey, William (Box 27)
  - Dixon, George E. (Box 27)
  - Dixon, Richard Watson (Box 27)
  - Doane, Florence V. (Box 28)
  - Doane, William Croswell (Box 28)
  - Dobson, Austin (Box 28)
  - Dodd, Anna Bowman Blake (Box 28)
  - Dodd, D.B.L. (Box 28)
  - Dodd, Edward William (Box 28)
  - Dodd, Frank Howard (Box 28)
  - Dodd, Mead & Co. (Box 28)
  - Dodge, Arthur Murray (Box 28)
  - Dodge, Cleveland Hoadley (Box 28)
  - Dodge, David Low (Box 28)
  - Dodge, David Stuart (Box 28)
  - Dodge, Eliza Whelpley (Box 28)
  - Dodge, Frederic Nevins (Box 28)
  - Dodge, Grace Hoadley (Box 28)
  - Dodge, Kate (Box 28)
  - Dodge, Marcellus Hartley (Box 29)
  - Dodge, Mary Abigail (Box 29)
  - Dodge, Mary Barker (Box 29)
  - Dodge, Mary Mapes (Box 29)
  - Dodge, Melissa Phelps (Mrs. Wm. E. Dodge) (Box 29)
  - Dodge, Sarah Cleveland (Mrs. David L.) (Box 29)
  - Dodge, Sarah Frances (Box 29)
  - Dodge, Walter Phelps (Box 29)
  - Dodge, William. Earl (Box 29)
  - Dodge, William Earl, Jr. (Box 29)
  - Dole, Nathan Haskell (Box 30)
  - Domett, Alfred (Box 30)
  - Domett, Henry W. (Box 30)
  - Donaldson, Julia Vaux (Box 30)
  - Donaldson, Susan L. (Box 30)
  - Donner, H. Montague (Box 30)
  - Dooley, A.H. (Box 30)
  - Derr, Julia Caroline Ripley (Box 30)
  - Dorrance, James French (Box 30)
  - Doubleday, Frank Nelson (Box 30)
  - Doughty, T.M.V. (Box 30)
  - Douglas, George (Box 30)
  - Douglas, Kate Percy (Box 30)
  - Dove, S.E. (Box 30)
  - Doveton, B. (Box 30)
  - Downing, Andrew (Box 30)
  - Doyle, Edward (Box 30)
  - Drake, Alexander Wilson (Box 31)
  - Drake, Charles Daniel (Box 31)
  - Drake, Edith True (Mrs Alexander W.) (Box 31)
  - Drake, James Madison (Box 31)
  - Draper, W.S. (Box 31)
  - Dreer, Ferdinand J. (Box 31)
  - Dreiser, Theodore (Box 31)
  - Drisler, Henry (Box 31)
  - Drysdalei, J. Buchanan (Box 31)
  - Du Bois, Henri R. (Box 31)
  - Du Bois, John C. (Box 31)
  - Dubois, Wilbur (Box 31)
  - Dudley, Henry (Box 31)
  - Duer, Caroline_ (Box 31)
  - Duffield & Company (Box 31)
  - Dunbar, Elizabeth (Box 31)
  - Dunn, Charles B. (Box 31)
  - Dunn, Jacob P., Jr. (Box 31)
  - Durand, A.C. (Box 31)
  - Durand, Henry S. (Box 31)
  - Durand, John S (Box 31)
  - Durant, Thomas Clark (Box 31)
  - Dusenberry, Annie S. (Box 31)
  - Dunsenberry, Victoria McCollum (Box 31)
  - Dusenbury, Mrs. M.E. (Box 31)
  - Dwight, Jane Wakeman Skinner (Mrs. Timothy) (Box 31)
  - Dwight, John Sullivan (Box 31)
  - Dwight, Theodore F (Box 31)
  - Dwight, Timothy (Box 31)
  - Deyer, Eleanor L. (Box 31)
  - Easter, Marguerite Elizabeth (Box 31)
  - Eastman, Annie H. (Box 31)
  - Eastmant Elaine Goodale (Box 31)
  - Easton, Alexander Nelson (Box 31)
  - Easton, Henry Clement (Box 31)
  - Easton. Mary Burnet Kinney (Mrs Nelson) (Box 31)
  - Easton, Nelson Starin (Box 31)
  - Eastwood, Ida M. (Box 31)
  - Eaton, Arthur Wentworth Hamilton (Box 31)
  - Eaton, William (Box 31)
  - Edgar, Howard (Box 32)
  - Edmonds, John (Box 32)
  - Edmondson, J.M. (Box 32)
  - Edmunds, George Franklin (Box 32)
  - Edwards, George Wharton (Box 32)
  - Edwards, Harry (Box 32)
  - Egan, Maurice.Francis (Box 32)
  - Eggleston, Edward (Box 32)
  - Eggleston, George Cary (Box 32)
  - Egtinge, Samuel (Box 32)
  - Eital, Henry (Box 32)
  - Elbel, O. Marion (Box 32)
  - Elder, Ella L. (Box 32)
  - Elder Publishing Co. (Box 32)
  - Elderkin, John (Box 32)
  - Eliot, Charles William (Box 32)
  - Eliot, Henrietta Robins (Mrs Thomas I.) (Box 32)
  - Eliot, Thomas Lamb (Box 32)
  - Ellard, Virginia G. (Box 32)
  - Elliot, Charles N. (Box 32)
  - Elliot, George Tracy (Box 32)
  - Elliott, Samuel (Box 32)
  - Elliott, Sarah Barnwell (Box 32)
  - Ellsworth, Erastus W. (Box 32)
  - Ellsworth, William W. (Box 32)
  - Ellwanger, George H. (Box 32)
  - Ellwanger, William De Lancey (Box 32)
  - Ely, George W. (Box 32)
  - Ely, Joseph A. (Box 32)
  - Ely,. W.W. (Box 32)
  - Emerson, Edward Waldo (Box 33)
  - Emery, Parcy Melville (Box 33)
  - Erskine, John (Box 33)
  - Erwin, R.W. (Box 33)
  - Estes & Lauriat (Box 33)
  - Evans, Thomas Coke (Box 33)
  - Eveleth, G.W. (Box 33)
  - Ewell, J.N. (Box 33)
  - Ewell & Clarke (Box 33)
  - Fabbri, Edith S. (Box 33)
  - Fahnestock, Harris Charles (Box 33)
  - Fairman, W.J. (Box 33)
  - Fairweather, Uha W. (Box 33)
  - Farley, Marian A. Thayer (Box 33)
  - Farragut, Loyall (Box 33)
  - Fassio, Cornelius (Box 33)
  - Fawcett, Edgar (Box 33)
  - Fearing, Lilian Blanche (Box 33)
  - Fearnley, John F. (Box 33)
  - Feder, Roy S. (Box 33)
  - Fellowes, Frank. Wayland (Box 33)
  - Fenollosa, Ernest F. (Box 33)
  - Fergus, Jessie (Box 33)
  - Fergus, John (Box 33)
  - Ferguson, Charles E. (Box 33)
  - Ferris, Floyd (Box 33)
  - Ferris, Mary L.D. (Box 33)
  - Festelitz, Katharine (Box 33)
  - Field, Eugene (Box 34)
  - Field, Henry Martyn (Box 34)
  - Field, Ju1ia Comstock (Mrs Eugene) (Box 34)
  - Field, Kate (Box 34)
  - Field, Mary J. (Box 34)
  - Field, Theodore W. (Box 34)
  - Fields, Annie Adams (Mrs James T) (Box 34)
  - Fields, James Thomas (Box 34)
  - Fields, Osgood & Co. (Box 34)
  - Finch, Edward Ridley (Box 35)
  - Finch, Julia Neely (Box 35)
  - Finch, Lucine (Box 35)
  - Finley, John Huston (Box 35)
  - Finney, C.G. (Box 35)
  - Finny, Bessie (Box 35)
  - Fisher, E.R (Box 35)
  - Fisher, George Park (Box 35)
  - Fisher, Grace (Box 35)
  - Fisher, Kate B. (Box 35)
  - Fiske, Harrison Grey (Box 35)
  - Fiske, Minnie Maddern (Box 35)
  - Fitch, George Hamlin (Box 35)
  - Flagg, William J. (Box 35)
  - Flash, Alexander (Box 35)
  - Flash, Harry Lynden (Box 35)
  - Fleming, Maybury (Box 35)
  - Fletcher, Austin Barclay (Box 35)
  - Flood, Theodore. L. (Box 35)
  - Florence, William Jermyn (Box 35)
  - Flugel, Ewald (Box 35)
  - Foley, Patrick Kevin (Box 35)
  - Foote, Lucius H (Box 35)
  - Foote, Mary Hallock (Box 35)
  - Forchheimer, Sara (Box 35)
  - Ford, Emily Ellsworth Gowler (Box 35)
  - Ford,. Gordon Lester (Box 35)
  - Ford, Harry P. (Box 35)
  - Ford, Isaac Nelson (Box 35)
  - Ford, Paul Leicester (Box 35)
  - Fords, Howard, & Hulbert (Box 35)
  - Forman, Alfred (Box 35)
  - Foss, San Walter (Box 35)
  - Foster, Morrison (Box 35)
  - Foster, William E. (Box 35)
  - Fowler, Frank. (Box 35)
  - Fox, George W. (Box 35)
  - Fox, Duffield & Co. (Box 35)
  - Francillon, Robert Edward (Box 36)
  - Francis, David G. (Box 36)
  - Franzén, Augustus (Box 36)
  - Fraser, John (Box 36)
  - Fraser, McPherson (Box 36)
  - Fraser, W. Lewis (Box 36)
  - Freeman, Mary Eleanor Wilkins (Box 36)
  - French, Ben F. (Box 36)
  - French, E.M.C. (Box 36)
  - French, J.L. (Box 36)
  - French, Josephine B. (Box 36)
  - French, Julia R. (Box 36)
  - French, Lillie Hamilton (Box 36)
  - Frothingham, Octavius Brooks (Box 36)
  - Fry, Horace B. (Box 36)
  - Frye, Eunice N. (Box 36)
  - Frye, William Pierce (Box 36)
  - Fuller, Henry H. (Box 37)
  - Fuller, James Ebenezer (Box 37)
  - Fuller, Louise (Box 37)
  - Fuller, Margaret Witter (Box 37)
  - Fuller, Rebecca Hope (Box 37)
  - Fuller, W.H. (Box 37)
  - Funk, Isaac Kauffman (Box 37)
  - Funk & Wagnalls, Publishers (Box 37)
  - Furbish, Julia (Box 37)
  - Furness, Horace Howard (Box 37)
  - Furness, Horace Howard,Jr. (Box 37)
  - Gable, William F. (Box 37)
  - Gale, Zona (Box 37)
  - Gallup, Charles (Box 37)
  - Gammell, W. (Box 37)
  - Gardiner, C.C. (Box 38)
  - Gardiner, William C. (Box 38)
  - Gardner, William Henry (Box 38)
  - Garland, Hamlin (Box 38)
  - Garland, Mary (Box 38)
  - Garrigus, Lewis C. (Box 38)
  - Garrison, Wendell Philips (Box 38)
  - Gastelbondo A., Carlos (Box 38)
  - Gay, Frank (Box 38)
  - Gay, Harry Nelson (Box 38)
  - Gay, Sydney Howard (Box 38)
  - Geblin, M.J. (Box 38)
  - Gentry, Thomas G. (Box 38)
  - Gerberding, Elizabeth Sears Bates (Box 38)
  - Gerelds, F.L. (Box 38)
  - Germond, H.S. (Box 38)
  - Gerry Philip (Box 38)
  - Gibson, George Rutledge (Box 39)
  - Gibson, Montgomery (Box 39)
  - Giddings, Franklin Henry (Box 39)
  - Gilbert, Edward (Box 39)
  - Gilchrist, Herbert Harlakenden (Box 39)
  - Gilder, Helena de Kay (Mrs Richard W.) (Box 39)
  - Gilder, Jeannette L. (Box 39)
  - Gilder, Joseph B. (Box 40)
  - Gilder, Richard Watson (1871-1883) (Box 41)
  - Gilder, Richard Watson (1884-1893) (Box 42)
  - Gilder, Richard Watson (1894-1909) (Box 43)
  - Gildersleeve, Basil Lanneau (Box 44)
  - Giles, Julia (Box 44)
  - Gill, Laura Drake (Box 44)
  - Gill, William Fearing (Box 44)
  - Gillespie, Jeannette Bliss (Box 44)
  - Gillett, Arthur Lincoln (Box 44)
  - Gillette, Annie Shepard (Box 44)
  - Gilley, F.W. (Box 44)
  - Gillilligan, Samuel (Box 44)
  - Gillington, Alice E. (Box 44)
  - Gilman, Arthur (Box 44)
  - Gilman, Charlotte Perkins Statson (Box 44)
  - Gilman, Daniel Coit (Box 44)
  - Gilman, Elizabeth Dwight Woolsey (Box 44)
  - Gilman, Nicholas Paine (Box 44)
  - Gilman, William C. (Box 44)
  - Gilmore, James Roberts (Box 44)
  - Gilmore, Joseph Henry (Box 44)
  - Ginn & Company (Box 44)
  - Gladden, George (Box 44)
  - Glumer, Frances Amelia Bartlet de Oviedo (Box 44)
  - Goddard, H.F. (Box 45)
  - Goddard, Minna G. (Box 45)
  - Godkin, Edwin L. (Box 45)
  - Godwin, Parke (Box 45)
  - Goetz, Philip Becker (Box 45)
  - Good, Jessie M. (Box 45)
  - Goodale, Dora Read (Box 45)
  - Goodchild, John Arthur (Box 45)
  - Goodell, Thomas Dwight (Box 45)
  - Goodsell, J.H. and C.M. (Box 45)
  - Goodwin, George B. (Box 45)
  - Goodwin, Maud Wilder (Box 45)
  - Gookin, Frederick H. (Box 45)
  - Gordon, Armistead (Box 45)
  - Gordon, Fred (Box 45)
  - Gosse, (Sir), Edmund William (Box 45)
  - Gottheil, Gustav (Box 45)
  - Gotthold, Florence (Box 45)
  - W.S. Gottsberger & Co. (Box 45)
  - Gottschalk, L.F. (Box 45)
  - Gould, Abbie (Box 45)
  - Gould, Charles W. (Box 45)
  - Gould, Elizabeth Porter (Box 45)
  - Gould, George Milbry (Box 45)
  - Gould, Jay (Box 45)
  - Gould, Laura Woodworth Stedman (Box 45)
  - Graham, James Lorimer, Jr. (Box 46)
  - Granbery, Nellie (Box 46)
  - Grant, Finlay A. (Box 46)
  - Grant, John Cameron (Box 46)
  - Grant, Robert (Box 46)
  - Gray, David (Box 46)
  - Grey, John Miller (Box 46)
  - Greeley, Horace (Box 46)
  - Green, George Walton (Box 46)
  - Green, Mason A. (Box 46)
  - Green, Samuel Abbott (Box 46)
  - Green, Thomas Edward (Box 46)
  - Greene, Charles S. (Box 46)
  - Greene, Homer (Box 46)
  - Greene, Mary Hulett Young (Box 46)
  - Greene, Sarah Pratt McLean (Box 46)
  - Greene, W. Maxwell (Box 46)
  - Greenslet, Ferris (Box 46)
  - Greenwaid, Mrs. Mattie (Box 46)
  - Gregory, Daniel S (Box 46)
  - Gregory, Sue (Box 46)
  - Griffin, Beatrice (Box 46)
  - Griffing, William B. (Box 46)
  - Griffith, Virginia R. (Box 46)
  - S.C. Griggs & Co. (Box 46)
  - Grindlay, James G. (Box 46)
  - Grinnell, John Willis (Box 46)
  - Grissen, Charles (Box 46)
  - Groot, Ella (Box 46)
  - Grossmann, Edwina Booth (Box 46)
  - Grunwald, H. (Box 46)
  - Guernsey, Clara F. (Box 46)
  - Guiney, Louise Imogen (Box 46)
  - Gummere, Francis Barton (Box 46)
  - Gurley, E.W. (Box 46)
  - Gurlitz, Augustus T (Box 46)
  - Gustafson, Zadel Barnes (Box 46)
  - Gutekunst, F. (Box 46)
  - Guyer, William Harris (Box 46)
  - Gwillim, R.B. (Box 46)
  - Habberton, John (Box 47)
  - Hackett, Frank Warren (Box 47)
  - Hackett, James Ketalas (Box 47)
  - Hackett, William H. (Box 47)
  - Hadley, Arthur T (Box 47)
  - Hadley, James (Box 47)
  - Hagen, O.A. (Box 47)
  - Hager, J. Henry (Box 47)
  - Hague, James Duncan (Box 47)
  - Haight, Louis (Box 47)
  - Hake, Thomas Gordon (Box 47)
  - Hale, Edward Everett, Jr. (Box 47)
  - Hale, Horatio Emmons (Box 47)
  - Hale, William Henry (Box 47)
  - Hall, Bolton (Box 47)
  - Hall, Earl N. (Box 47)
  - Hall,·F.L. (Box 47)
  - Hall, Florence Howe (Box 47)
  - Hall, Fred J. (Box 47)
  - Hall, Gertrude (Box 48)
  - Hall, Henry (Box 48)
  - Hall, John D. (Box 48)
  - Hall, Mary Osborne (Box 48)
  - Hall., Richard Boylston (Box 48)
  - Hallett, Samuel (Box 48)
  - Hallett, W.T. (Box 48)
  - Halsey, Francis Whiting (Box 48)
  - Hamersley, John W. (Box 48)
  - Hamilton, A.C. (Box 48)
  - Hamlin, Sarah D. (Box 48)
  - Hammond, Harry P. (Box 48)
  - Hammnond, Marie Johns (Box 48)
  - Hammond, William Alexander (Box 48)
  - Hanks, Edwin J. (Box 48)
  - Hansbrough, May Berri (Chapman) (Box 48)
  - Harbaugh, Thomas Chalmers (Box 48)
  - Harben, William Nathaniel (Box 48)
  - Harbour, Jefferson Lee (Box 48)
  - Harby, Lee Cohen (Box 48)
  - Harby, Lewis R (Box 48)
  - Hardinge, Bertha Wilson (Box 48)
  - Hardy, Arthur Sherburne (Box 48)
  - Hardy, Henry C. (Box 48)
  - Hare, Mrs. G.H. (Box 48)
  - Hargrove, C.R. (Box 48)
  - Harland, Aline V. (Box 49)
  - Harland, Edward (Box 49)
  - Harland, Henry (Box 49)
  - Harland, Irene Z. (Box 50)
  - Harland, Thomas (Box 50)
  - Harlow, Elizabeth D. (Box 50)
  - Harney, Will Wallace (Box 50)
  - Harper, Joseph Henry (Box 50)
  - Harper, .Joseph S. Jr (Box 50)
  - Harper & Brothers (Box 50)
  - Harrihill, Arthur (Box 50)
  - Herrington, Karl P. (Box 50)
  - Harriot, S. Carman (Box 50)
  - Harris, Frank (Box 50)
  - Harris, George R. (Box 50)
  - Harris, George William (Box 50)
  - Harris, Hattie Starr (Box 50)
  - Harris, Mary Pickering (Box 50)
  - Harris, Miriam Coles (Box 50)
  - Harris, Robert L. (Box 50)
  - Harris, Thomas Aston (Box 50)
  - Harris, Tudon Read (Box 50)
  - Harris, William Torrey (Box 50)
  - Harrison, Birge (Box 51)
  - Harrison, Burton N. (Box 51)
  - Harrison, Carter R. (Box 51)
  - Harrison, Caskie (Box 51)
  - Harrison, Constance Cary (Box 51)
  - Harrison, Francis Burton (Box 51)
  - Harrison, Gabriel (Box 51)
  - Harrison, James Albert (Box 51)
  - Harrison, Susie Frances Riley (Box 51)
  - Hart, Beatrice Harrison Herter, Albert (Box 51)
  - Hart, Charles Henry (Box 51)
  - Hart, James Morgan (Box 51)
  - Hart, Jerome Alfred (Box 51)
  - Hart, Percie William Edward (Box 51)
  - Hart, Theodore (Box 51)
  - Hartmann, Sadakichi (Box 51)
  - Harvey, George Brinton McClellan (Box 51)
  - Harvey, J.C. (Box 51)
  - Harwood, Isabelle (Box 51)
  - Hassard, Isabel E.H. (Box 52)
  - Hassard, John R.G. (Box 52)
  - Harch, Lorenzo J. (Box 52)
  - Haven, M. Emily (Box 52)
  - Haviland, Augustus (Box 52)
  - Hawkes, Clarence (Box 52)
  - Hawkins, Willis Brooks (Box 52)
  - Hawthorne, Hildegarde (Box 52)
  - Hawthorne, Julian (Box 52)
  - Hay, Clara L. Stone (Box 52)
  - Hay, John Milton (Box 52)
  - Hay, Lucia C. (Box 52)
  - Hayes, Augustus Allan (Box 52)
  - Hayes, Ednah Proctor Clarke (Box 52)
  - Hayes, John Russell (Box 52)
  - Hayne, Mary Middleton Michel (Box 52)
  - Hayne, Paul. Hamilton (Box 52)
  - Hayne, William Hamilton (Box 52)
  - Hays, Jenny Ward (Box 52)
  - Hazard., Caroline (Box 52)
  - Hazeltine, Mayo Williamson (Box 52)
  - Hazelton, Byrd (Box 52)
  - Hazelton, George C., Jr. (Box 52)
  - Hazen, A.W. (Box 52)
  - Head, Franklin Harvey (Box 53)
  - Headley, G.T. (Box 53)
  - Hearn, Lafcadio (Box 53)
  - D.C. Heath & Co. (Box 53)
  - Heath, Frederic M. (Box 53)
  - Heath, Kate Adams (Box 53)
  - Heaton, .John Langdon (Box 53)
  - Hedge, Frederic Henry (Box 54)
  - Heinemann, William (Box 54)
  - Helder, J. (Box 54)
  - Hellman, Frances (Box 54)
  - Hellman, George S. (Box 54)
  - Helmick, Elizabeth M. (Box 54)
  - Henderson, George (Box 54)
  - Henderson, Hannan B. (Box 54)
  - Henderson, Isaac (Box 54)
  - Henderson, W.W. (Box 54)
  - Hendrick, Burton J. (Box 54)
  - Hendrick,. Leonard A. (Box 54)
  - Hennessy, William John (Box 54)
  - Henry, Charles, P. (Box 54)
  - Henry, J.A. (Box 54)
  - Herbert, J. (Box 54)
  - Hereford, Oliver (Box 54)
  - Herrick, Robert (Box 54)
  - Herter, Albert (Box 54)
  - Herwig, I.A. (Box 54)
  - Hickox, Chauncey (Box 55)
  - Hicks, Gilbert H. (Box 55)
  - Hicks, Thomas (Box 55)
  - Higginson, Ella Rhoades (Box 55)
  - Higginson, James T. (Box 55)
  - Higginson, Thomas Wentworth (Box 55)
  - Hildreth, Charles Lotin (Box 55)
  - Hildrith, Julia Kyle (Box 55)
  - Hill, Adams Sherman (Box 56)
  - Hill, Edmund (Box 56)
  - Hill, Edwin Bliss (Box 56)
  - Hill, Frederick Trevor (Box 56)
  - Hill, George (Box 56)
  - Hill, Joseph M. (Box 56)
  - Hill, Julia C.M. (Box 56)
  - Hill, Mabel Wood (Box 56)
  - Hill, Mary (Box 56)
  - Hillard, Kate (Box 56)
  - Hills, Agnes N. (Box 56)
  - Hills, Alfred C. (Box 56)
  - Hinkley, Mary L. (Box 56)
  - Hinton, Henry L. (Box 56)
  - Hinton, Richard J (Box 56)
  - Hitchcock, A.B.C. (Box 56)
  - Hitchcock, Hiram (Box 56)
  - Hitchcock, Norman (Box 56)
  - Hitchcock, Ripley (Box 56)
  - Hitchcock, Roswell Dwight (Box 56)
  - Hitt, Robert Reynolds (Box 56)
  - Hittell, John Sherzer (Box 56)
  - Hodgdon, Julia A. (Box 57)
  - Hodgins, Fred B. (Box 57)
  - Hoe, Robert (Box 57)
  - Holbrook, Levi (Box 57)
  - Holland, Josiah Gilbert (Box 57)
  - Holley, Marietta (Box 57)
  - Holliday, Samuel N. (Box 57)
  - Holman, Stephan (Box 57)
  - Holmes, .John Haynes (Box 57)
  - Holmes, Oliver Wendell (Box 57)
  - Holt, George Chandler (Box 57)
  - Holt, H.P.R. (Box 57)
  - Holt, Hamilton (Box 57)
  - Holt, Henry (Box 57)
  - Homans, J. Smith (Box 57)
  - Homer, Winslow (Box 57)
  - Hooper, Miles Morrison (Box 57)
  - Hopkins, Fred M. (Box 57)
  - Hopkins, George (Box 57)
  - Hopkins, Rosina M. (Box 57)
  - Horder, W. Garrett (Box 58)
  - Horne, Herbert P. (Box 58)
  - Horne, Richard Hengist (Box 58)
  - Horton, George (Box 58)
  - Hosmer, George Washington (Box 58)
  - Hotchkiss, M.I. (Box 58)
  - Houck, E.E. (Box 58)
  - Hiugh, Harris (Box 58)
  - Houghton, A.F. (Box 58)
  - Houghton, Henry Oscar (Box 58)
  - H.O. Houghton & Co. (Box 58)
  - Houghton, Louise (Box 58)
  - Houghton, W.A. (Box 58)
  - Houghton, Mifflin & Co. (Box 59)
  - Houghton, Osgood & Co (Box 60)
  - House, Edward Howard (Box 60)
  - House, Kato (Box 60)
  - Houston, J.B. (Box 60)
  - Hovenden, John (Box 61)
  - Hovendon, Thomas (Box 61)
  - Hovey, Harrietta Farnham Spofford (Box 61)
  - Hove, Henriette Russell (Box 61)
  - Hovey, Richard (Box 61)
  - Hovey, S. (Box 61)
  - Howard, Alice Wyndham (Mrs Bronson) (Box 61)
  - Howard, Blanche Willis (Box 61)
  - Howard, Bronson (Box 61)
  - Howard, Henry Ward Beecher (Box 61)
  - Howard, James Q. (Box 61)
  - Howard, John Raymond (Box 61)
  - Howe, Julia Ward (Box 61)
  - Howe, Mark Anthony DeWolfe (Box 61)
  - Howe, Walter (Box 61)
  - Howe, Will D (Box 61)
  - Howe, Will H (Box 61)
  - Howells, Mildred (Box 61)
  - Howells, William Dean (Box 61)
  - Howland, Edward (Box 62)
  - Howland, Emma F (Box 62)
  - Howland, Frances Louise Morse (Box 62)
  - Howland, George (Box 62)
  - Howland, Henry Elias (Box 62)
  - Howland, Marie (Box 62)
  - Hubbard, S.A. (Box 63)
  - Hubbard, Thomas H (Box 63)
  - Hudson, Thomas (Box 63)
  - Huffman, William F (Box 63)
  - Hughes, Charles Evans (Box 63)
  - Hughes, .John (Box 63)
  - Hughes, Rupert (Box 63)
  - Hull, C.P. (Box 63)
  - Hull, H.S. (Box 63)
  - Humbert, E.C. (Box 63)
  - Hunt, Catherine C. Howland (Box 63)
  - Hunt, Rachelle Gibbons (Box 63)
  - Hunt, Sollace (Box 63)
  - Hunt, Theodore Whitefield (Box 63)
  - Hunt, William T (Box 63)
  - Hunter, Catharine (Box 63)
  - Hunter, H.C. (Box 63)
  - Huntington, Charles B (Box 63)
  - Huntington, Charles Stuart (Box 63)
  - Huntington, Collis Potter (Box 63)
  - Huntington, Frederick J. (Box 63)
  - Huntington, Julia Stuart Dodge (Box 63)
  - Huntington, P. Webster (Box 63)
  - Huntington, W.H. (Box 63)
  - Huntington, William Reed (Box 63)
  - Huntington, William S (Box 63)
  - Hurd, A.D (Box 63)
  - Hurd, M.M. (Box 63)
  - Hurd & Roughton (Box 63)
  - Hurlbert, William Henry (Box 63)
  - Hurst, John Fletcher (Box 63)
  - Hussey, Cornelia Collins (Box 63)
  - Hutchinson, Ellen Mackay [n.d.] (Box 64)
  - Hutchinson, Ellen Mackay (1880-1905) (Box 65)
  - Hutchinson, Thomas (Box 66)
  - Hutton, Eleanor (Box 66)
  - Hutton, Lawrence (Box 66)
  - Hyde, George Merriam (Box 66)
  - Hyde, Gertrude Stewart (Box 66)
  - Iddings, Lewis Morris (Box 66)
  - Ingalls, John James (Box 66)
  - Ingham, John H. (Box 66)
  - Ingvall, Aron (Box 66)
  - Irving, Minnie (Box 66)
  - Irwin, Thomas Caulfield (Box 66)
  - Isaacs, Abram Samuel (Box 66)
  - Isham, Catherine G. Stedman (Box 66)
  - Ives, Brayton (Box 66)
  - Ives, C.B. (Box 66)
  - Jaccaci, August Floriano (Box 67)
  - Jaccaci, Mabel Thayer (Box 67)
  - Jackson, H.A. (Box 67)
  - Jackson, Stuart Wells (Box 67)
  - Jacobi, Mary Putnam (Box 67)
  - Jacobs, Joseph (Box 67)
  - James, Alice Archer Sewall (Box 67)
  - James, George Wharton (Box 67)
  - James, Sir Kingston (Box 67)
  - Jameson, J.A. (Box 67)
  - Janvier, Catherine Ann Drinker (Box 67)
  - Janvier, Margaret Thomson (Box 68)
  - Janvier, Thomas A. (Box 68)
  - Japp, Alexander Hay (Box 68)
  - Jarves, James .J (Box 68)
  - Jay, Elizabeth Clarkson (Box 68)
  - Jefferson, Joseph (Box 68)
  - Jenkins, Howard Malcolm (Box 68)
  - Jenkins, Robert E (Box 68)
  - Jenks, Tudor (Box 68)
  - Jennison, Lucy White (Box 68)
  - Jennison, Samuel (Box 68)
  - Jessup, Alexander (Box 68)
  - Jewett, Sarah Orne (Box 68)
  - Jewett, Sophie (Box 68)
  - Johnes, Mary de M. (Box 69)
  - Johnson, Arnold B (Box 69)
  - Johnson, Gurgess (Box 69)
  - Johnson, Charles Frederick (Box 69)
  - Johnson, Eastman (Box 69)
  - Johnson, Earlham (Box 69)
  - Johnson, Eleanor (Box 69)
  - Johnson, Elizabeth (Box 69)
  - Johnson, Emily Pauline (Box 69)
  - Johnson, Helen Louise Kendrick (Box 69)
  - Johnson, Jane A (Box 69)
  - Johnson, Julia Cleveland White (Box 69)
  - Johnson, Mabel (Box 69)
  - Johnson, Mary Stedman (Box 69)
  - Johnson, Oliver (Box 69)
  - Johnson, Owen (Box 69)
  - Johnson, Robert Underwood (1874-1879) (Box 69)
  - Johnson, Robert Underwood (1880-1889) (Box 70)
  - Johnson, Robert Underwood (1900-1905) (Box 71)
  - Johnson, Robert Underwood (1906-1923) (Box 72)
  - Johnson, Rossiter (Box 72)
  - Johnson, T. (Box 73)
  - Johnson, Virginia Wales (Box 73)
  - Johnson, Walter S (Box 73)
  - Johnson, William Woolsey (Box 73)
  - Johnston, A. (Box 73)
  - Johnston, J.H. (Box 73)
  - Johnston, Richard Malcolm (Box 73)
  - Johnston, William Preston (Box 73)
  - Jones, Amanda Theodosia (Box 73)
  - Jones, Charles Colcock (Box 73)
  - Jones, Jenkin Lloyd (Box 73)
  - Jones, Jessamine L (Box 73)
  - Jones, L.E. (Box 73)
  - Jones, Mary H (Box 73)
  - Jones, W.D. (Box 73)
  - Jones, William P (Box 73)
  - Jones, Willard D (Box 73)
  - Jordan, David Starr (Box 73)
  - Jordan, William George (Box 73)
  - Joy, Albert Bruce (Box 73)
  - Joy, James Frederick (Box 73)
  - Kalbfleisch, Emma A. (Box 73)
  - Kalbfleisch, Maud (Box 73)
  - Kalishe, Frances (Box 73)
  - Kasson, John Adam (Box 73)
  - Kauffman, Reginald Wright (Box 73)
  - Kavaugh, Jessamine (Box 73)
  - Keasbey, Anthony Quinton (Box 73)
  - Keeler, Charles Augustus (Box 73)
  - Keenan, Henry Francis (Box 73)
  - Kehoe, Edward (Box 73)
  - Kelley, Edgar Stillman (Box 73)
  - Kelley, James P. (Box 73)
  - Kelly, William V. (Box 73)
  - Kellog, Miner Kilbourne (Box 73)
  - Kendall, May (Box 74)
  - Kennan, George (Box 74)
  - Kennedy, William Sloane (Box 74)
  - Kent, Henry Watson (Box 74)
  - Kent, William (Box 74)
  - Kenyon, Elvira (Box 74)
  - Kenyon, James Benjamin (Box 74)
  - Kenyon, W.C. (Box 74)
  - Keppel, Frederick (Box 74)